const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Put these sentences in indirect speech"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:'He said, "Where is Kate going?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked where Kate was going.",2:"He asked where was Kate going.",3:"He asked where Kate went."}},{type:"test",question:'Arman said, "Where do you live, Ann?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Arman asked Ann where she lived.",2:"Arman asked Ann if she did live.",3:"Arman asked Ann if she lived."}},{type:"test",question:'The doctor asked, "How do you feel?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"The doctor asked how I felt.",2:"The doctor asked how did I feel.",3:"The doctor asked how I had felt."}},{type:"test",question:`"Why hasn't he done his homework?" the teacher said.`,rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"The teacher asked why he hadn't done his homework.",2:"The teacher asked why he hasn't done his homework.",3:"The teacher asked why he didn't do his homework."}},{type:"test",question:'"Where is the nearest bus stop?" the old man addressed me.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"The old man asked me where the nearest bust stop was.",2:"The old man asked me if the nearest bus stop was near.",3:"The old man asked me where the nearest bus stop is."}},{type:"test",question:'Lena asked, "Who wrote this book?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Lena asked who had written this book.",2:"Lena asked who did write this book.",3:"Lena asked if this book wrote."}},{type:"test",question:'They said, " What time does the train start?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"They asked what time the train started.",2:"They asked what time the train starts.",3:"They asked what time does the train start."}},{type:"test",question:'She asked me, "What will you do tomorrow?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked me what I would do the next day.",2:"She asked me what will I did the next day.",3:"She asked me what will I do the next day."}},{type:"test",question:'I asked my uncle, "How long did you stay in Astana?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"I asked my uncle how long he had stayed in Astana.",2:"I asked my uncle how long did he stay in Astana.",3:"I asked my uncle how long he stayed in Astana."}},{type:"test",question:'He wondered, "Where did you buy this hat?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He wondered where I had bought that hat.",2:"He wondered where I bought that hat.",3:"He wondered where I bought that hat."}},{type:"test",question:'He said to her, "Where do you usually spend your summer holidays?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked her where she usually spent her summer holidays.",2:"He asked her where does she usually spend her summer holidays.",3:"He asked her where did she usually spend her summer holidays."}},{type:"test",question:'She asked me, "Why did you come here yesterday?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked me why I had come here the previous day.",2:"She asked me why did I come here the previous day.",3:"She asked me why had I come here the previous day."}},{type:"test",question:'"What are you trying to teach them?" Alisa asked.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Alisa asked what I was trying to teach them.",2:"Alisa asked what I am trying to teach them.",3:"Alisa asked I was trying to teach them what."}},{type:"test",question:'"What tooth is giving you trouble?" asked the doctor.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"The doctor asked what tooth was giving me trouble.",2:"The doctor asked what tooth is giving me trouble.",3:"The doctor asked what tooth gave me trouble."}},{type:"test",question:'"Why are you whistling?" said Father.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Father asked why I was whistling.",2:"Father asked if I was whistling.",3:"Father asked I was whistling."}}]}]};export{e as default};
